Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lizza-ranit-655b72116 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Registered Nurses

Customer Service

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Pediatric) (CCRN-P)

Neonatal Resuscitation Program

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Honors-Awards

UCLA Health System Scholar

Lizza Ranit

BSN, RN, PCCN, CCRN

Greater New York City Area

Summary

Certified Registered Nurse with experience in pediatric critical care and adult cardiac surgery in level 1 trauma, academic medical centers. Able to provide compassionate and holistic patient care as part of multidisciplinary team to optimize patient experience and outcomes.

Experience

Columbia University Irving Medical Center Registered Nurse

February 2020 - Present (4 months)

New York Presbyterian/Morgan Stanley Children's Hospital 14 bed Neuro/Ortho Pediatric ICU in a level 1 pediatric trauma center

Ro Health

Registered Nurse

December 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Providing care to students with chronic diagnoses within the school setting, including enteral feeds, seizure monitoring, and diabetes management

UCLA Health

Registered Nurse

July 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

24 bed Pediatric ICU/CTICU in a high acuity, level 1 trauma center

Working with multidisciplinary team to provide complex, holistic, and developmentally appropriate care to critically ill children, from neonates to young adults, with varying diagnoses

Skill set includes titration of vasoactive drips in hemodynamically unstable patients, CRRT (NxStage), management of airway and lines (e.g. arterial line, central lines, external ventricular drain, foley) for invasive monitoring

Page 1 of 2

Preceptor for new hires (experienced nurses and new grads), travelers, and student nurses

Member of Bug Buster Committee - Unit champion for infection prevention

Stanford Health Care Registered Nurse September 2015 - June 2018 (2 years 10 months)

Cardiac Surgery IICU

Patient population includes valve replacements/repairs, coronary artery bypass graft surgeries, thoracic/aortic aneurysm repairs, heart/lung transplants, ventricular assist devices, general surgery, trauma, vascular, and bone marrow transplants.

Chair of Unit Diabetes Committee

UCLA Health Student Nurse March 2015 - June 2015 (4 months) UCLA Medical Center, Santa Monica

Senior nursing preceptorship in a Medical ICU and CCU, created an evidence based project that assessed the unit's current ventilator weaning trials

Education

University of California, Los Angeles
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2011 - 2015)